timtara.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Timtara and its affiliates respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by Timtara. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Timtara you agree to the collection and use of your data by Timtara in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

**We want you to**  
•    Feel comfortable using our website

•    Feel secure submitting information to us

•    Contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site

•    Know that by using our sites you are consenting to the collection of certain data

•    We are committed to protecting your personal privacy. Timtara will not give out your telephone number or email address, except where needed to deliver a product or service your order

•    We do not store any credit card details at our end. This information is collected primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to facilitate a truly personalized shopping experience

•     **COLLECTION of PERSONAL INFORMATION** : We collect "personal" information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product from us, we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number  and email address. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address. If you take advantage of special services offered by us, we may collect other personal information about you. We use your personal information for internal purposes such as processing and keeping you informed of your order

•   **  DISCLOSURE of PERSONAL INFORMATION:** Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your PII that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure. Otherwise, however, we will not disclose your name, address and other information which identifies you personally to any third party without your consent. We reserve the right to collect general demographic and other anonymous information that does not personally identify you. This information is not associated with your personally identifiable information and cannot be linked to you personally. However, in case of a situation wherein we are obliged to comply with law or a statutory obligation or a legal process, we would be compelled to provide information about a customer

•   **  OPT-OUT of further usage of PERSONAL INFORMATION:** If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, or you want us to remove any PII that we have collected about you, please unsubscribe at “http://www.timtara.com/subscribe.php?action=unsubscribe” or e-mail your request to customerfirst@timtara.com

•     **Why are COOKIES important:** We use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and clear gifs to store certain types of information each time you visit any page on our website. Cookies enable this website to recognize the information you have consented to give to this website and help us determine what portions of this website are most appropriate for your professional needs. We may also use cookies to serve advertising banners to you. These banners may be served by us or by a third party on our behalf. These cookies will not contain any personal information

•     **OPT-OUT of setting website cookie on users browsers:** Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies of disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non- functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on

•     **NPII advertising:** We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user

•     **OPT-OUT of NPII advertising:** If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s website by clicking http://www.networkadvertising.org/
